Do you have any tattoos?
你有纹身吗？
I don't.
我没有。
I've never been brave enough to go under the needle.
我从来没有足够的勇气去纹身。
But if you do have one, you are not alone.
但如果你有，你并不孤单。
According to a report by Experian, the number of tattoo parlours in Britain increased by 173% between 2004 and 2014.
益博睿（Experian）的一份报告显示，2004年至2014年间，英国的纹身店数量增长了173%。
Tattoos have always been controversial – personally and culturally.
纹身一直颇具争议——无论是在个人层面还是文化层面。
Some people love them and some hate them.
有人喜欢，也有人厌恶。
So, are they good or bad?
那么，纹身究竟是好是坏？
These days, one in five people in the UK has some ink – whether it's a commemorative date, a sleeve or a full body suit.
如今，英国五分之一的人都有纹身——无论是纪念日期、半袖纹身还是全身纹身。
What's responsible for this rise in popularity?
是什么让纹身如此流行？
"You see a lot of celebrities getting tattooed," says Lee Clements of the British Tattoo Artist Association speaking on BBC radio.
英国纹身艺术家协会的李·克莱门茨在BBC广播中表示：“你会看到很多名人纹身。”
As a result, people want to copy them or it becomes a fashion thing – certain tattoos become a trend.
因此，人们想要模仿他们，或者纹身成为一种时尚——某些纹身图案会成为潮流。
Employers have become more accepting of visible tats too.
雇主们对可见的纹身也变得更加宽容。
Last year, London's Metropolitan Police relaxed a ban on recruiting candidates with visible body art.
去年，伦敦警察局放宽了对招聘有可见纹身候选人的禁令。
And earlier this year, Air New Zealand said it would end a ban on body art to allow workers to express their individuality and cultural heritage.
今年早些时候，新西兰航空表示将取消对纹身的禁令，允许员工表达自己的个性和文化传承。
That said, not all employers would agree.
尽管如此，并非所有雇主都认同这一点。
Grace, 28, told the BBC that she had been offered jobs in sales, which were then withdrawn when employers saw her hand tattoo.
28岁的格雷丝告诉BBC，她曾获得过销售岗位的工作机会，但当雇主看到她手上的纹身后，offer被撤回了。
"It feels like having a tattoo is not socially acceptable," she says.
“感觉纹身在社会上是不被接受的，”她说。
"Having a tattoo does not amount to a protected characteristic," remarks Susan Harris, legal director at the GMB union, a UK trade union.
英国工会GMB的法律总监苏珊·哈里斯表示：“纹身并不是受保护的特征。”
This means a person can be dismissed for having one if it breaches the employer's dress code – except on religious grounds.
这意味着，除非出于宗教原因，否则如果纹身违反了雇主的着装规范，员工可能会因此被解雇。
And let's not forget the risk of infection.
此外，我们不要忘记感染的风险。
At present anyone in the UK can set up a parlour and offer procedures without proper training, a report from the Royal Society for Public Health says.
英国公共卫生学会的一份报告称，目前在英国，任何人都可以开设纹身店并提供纹身服务，无需接受适当的培训。
They note that just under 20% of those tattooed experience negative side effects, including swelling, burning or a skin infection.
报告指出，近20%的纹身者会经历副作用，包括肿胀、灼痛或皮肤感染。
It seems that attitudes to tattoos are changing, but they aren't quite there yet.
人们对纹身的态度似乎正在改变，但还没有完全转变。
Should you be persuaded to have one – visit a reputable tattoo artist with a portfolio.
如果你被说动想要纹身——一定要去找有作品集、信誉良好的纹身师。
Discuss your design with them and don't make a hasty decision!
和他们讨论你的设计，不要仓促做决定！
If you later regret it, your tattoo will need laser removal or a cover up.
如果之后后悔了，你需要通过激光去除纹身或者覆盖纹身。
Better get a temporary tattoo or henna tattoo first and see if you're happy with it.
最好先纹一个临时纹身或彩绘，看看自己是否满意。
Wear it for a few months and then decide.
几个月后再做决定。